cardstore.com 2010-04-01

# Greeting Cards, Invitations, Announcements, and Photocards

## Privacy Policy

This site was created by Cardstore.com, Inc. This entire site is copyright protected ©1999-2010 by Cardstore.com. All rights are reserved. Privacy policy updated February 16, 2010. 

Rest assured that the information you provide is safeguarded. Cardstore.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. We recognize that it is vitally important to act responsibly with your information. Cardstore.com does not sell or trade e-mail lists and Cardstore.com keeps your credit card and personal profile information is protected. 

At Cardstore.com, we have taken several steps to ensure that your personal and payment information is secure and your privacy is respected. One of those steps is telling you what information we collect, how we collect it, and how you can be removed from our mailing lists. Please read the following policy to understand how any information you provide to us is maintained and used as you make your purchases. This privacy policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

### IN GENERAL

When you shop on our site, your computer and our server send data back and forth in encrypted format that ensures the safety and security of your information. Cardstore.com will not disclose your personal information unless acting under a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Cardstore.com; (3) enforce the Cardstore.com Terms and Conditions of Use; or (4) act to protect the interests of its members or others.

If you come to Cardstore.com from a partner web site, make a purchase on Cardstore.com, and "opt-in" to receive information from that partner, we may share your name, address, and email address with that partner. If the partner is a gift card retailer, we may also share the value of the gift card purchased.

### WHY WE COLLECT CERTAIN INFORMATION

At Cardstore.com, we collect:

We collect this information in order to determine how to create the best experience for our customers. By looking at usage patterns, we learn which areas need more content and which areas are not meeting our customers' needs. In addition to the use of your information to operate the site, Cardstore.com also aggregates anonymous information which does not personally identify you, which may be used by Cardstore.com or shared with its advertisers. We also collect information to customize our features for individual visitors who opt to become members, notify consumers about updates to our Web site, and contact consumers for marketing purposes. Receiving e-mail notifications is always up to the customer. When you make a purchase or become a member, you can tell us whether or not you want to receive e-mail updates. We do not sell or trade our e-mail lists.

### YOUR NAME AND ADDRESSES: YOUR PERSONAL PROFILE

When you make your first purchase, you provide us your name and mailing addresses. Your e-mail address is used to verify your identity next time you come to our site, to confirm or otherwise update you about your order, to verify your credit billing information and, if you allow, to further communicate with you about our upcoming products, services and programs. They are not used for any other purpose.

You will receive special offers via e-mail from Cardstore.com or Cardstore.com's business partners only if you have indicated so in your profile. If you should choose in the future not to receive these special offers, please contact Cardstore.com via email at customercare@cardstore.com, or written request: 918 Parker Street, Berkeley, CA 94710.

### CREDIT CARD INFORMATION

Protecting your order information is our priority. Anytime we ask for credit card information, we transmit that information in an encrypted format using the industry-leading standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology.

SSL encrypts your order information to avoid the decoding of that information by anyone other than Cardstore.com. To check the security of that information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see the unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https."

Some versions of browsers and some firewalls don't permit communication via secure servers. In that case, you'll be unable to connect to the server, which means you won't be able to mistakenly place an order through an unsecured connection. If you cannot access the secure server for any reason, please e-mail us at info@cardstore.com.

To further protect your information, Cardstore.com does not store credit card information on its servers without your consent.

### TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION

We disclose your information to no third parties except to accomplish normal credit card and other similar payments, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. Unless you say so, we use your information solely to fulfill your order, transact your purchase, and help us improve our website and product offering to you. Notwithstanding any other provision to the contrary, Cardstore.com reserves the right to cooperate with local, state and federal officials in any investigation relating to any purported illegal activity(ies) and, when required by law, regulation, legal process or government requests, to disclose any personal information furnished by you or collected by Cardstore.com to law enforcement authorities or other relevant or related third parties.

### WAYS YOU CAN HELP KEEP YOUR INFORMATION PRIVATE AND SECURE

The most important step in maintaining your privacy is to secure your password. Choose a password that someone you know cannot easily guess (do not use friend or relative's name, other names related to you, or simple words out of a dictionary.) Change your password immediately if you suspect someone has been accessing your account or profile without your permission.

### WHAT ARE COOKIES AND HOW ARE THEY USED?

A cookie is a small piece of information that many websites use to help make shopping on-line easier. This information is sent to your browser from our web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Whenever you login, our server requires that your computer accept cookies.

We use cookies in order to improve your shopping experience. When you visit the Cardstore.com website, your cookie helps us keep track of your shopping preferences. Once you set up a profile, your cookie allows us to recognize you when you return to our site. You will be able to access your account information so you don't have to re-enter it. It also helps us keep track of your shopping basket. And, if you ask to receive e-mails from us, it helps us deliver them to you.

Your privacy and security are not compromised when you accept a cookie from the Cardstore.com website. If you reject cookies, Cardstore.com will track your session through a web-based session identifier. Either way, your information is yours and yours alone. No one else can access the information except Cardstore.com.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES AND SERVICES

The Cardstore.com website may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These websites have their own policies regarding privacy. You should review those policies when visiting the websites. Cardstore.com has no responsibility for linked websites and provides these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.

### CONTACT CARDSTORE

If you have any questions regarding privacy at Cardstore.com please notify us by e-mail at [privacy@Cardstore.com](mailto:privacy@cardstore.com).
